<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Game</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_board">board</string>
    <string name="title_activity_howtoplay">howtoplay</string>
    <string name="howtoplay_text"><b>Instructions </b> \n
        1.Game Setup \n
        2.How to play \n
        3.How to Capture \n
        4. How to win</string>
    <string name="title_activity_singleplayer">Singleplayer</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gamestatitics">gamestatitics</string>
    <string name="title_activity_savegame">savegame</string>
    <string name="title_activity_save_player">SavePlayer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_save_multiplayer">SaveMultiplayer</string>
     <string name="howToPlay">\n<b>Set Up</b>\n
Mossa is a game for two players.

The board is placed between the two players with the long sides facing them.  The six cups nearest each player belong to him or her and their larger scoring cups or tray is to the right.  Three gemstones are placed in each of the 12 cups.

\n\n<b>Object</b>\n
Each player attempts to collect as many pebbles as possible before one of the players clears his or her side of pebbles.

\n\n<b>Play</b>\n
Players alternate turns.  In his or her turn each player picks up all the pebbles from one cup on his or her side of the board and places them one by one in the cups around the board in a counter-clockwise direction, including his tray, but not in the opponent’s tray.  If the last pebble is placed in the player’s own tray, that player goes again.  If the last pebble is placed in an empty cup on the player’s own side, he or she may take all the gemstones from the opponent’s cup directly opposite that cup.  All the pebbles captured including the capturing pebble are placed in the players own tray.

\n\n<b>To Win</b>\n
The game is over when a player has no more pebbles in any of the cups on his/her side.  The remaining player then takes all the pebbles left on his/her side and places them into his/her mancala.  The winner is the player with the most pebbles in his/her mancala.</string>


</resources>
